

# **Matteo Massetti**

**Date of birth:** 16/12/1997 | **Nationality:** Italian | **Phone number:** 

(+39) 3771144748 (Mobile) | **Email address:** matteomassetti8@gmail.com

**Website:** https://matteomass.github.io/

Address: Via Mafalada di Savoia, 18/c, 06083, Bastia Umbra, Italy (Home)

# ABOUT ME

I'm a Software Engineer with a specific training in the field of Artificial Intelligence. My knowledge is not limited to this area but ranges in different areas of programming, such as blockchain and mobile programming. In two years of work experience I have gained and honed the skills needed to work effectively in teams.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

04/07/2021 - CURRENT Corciano, Italy

**SOFTWARE DEVELOPER MICRA S.R.L.** 

Full Stack Developer of products, services and platforms in banking and industry. Within the Research and Development group, I've contributed to the study of new technologies, including Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence, aimed at improving company's products and identifying new possibile solutions for the customers.

30/09/2018 - 30/12/2018

**INTERNSHIP** UNIVERSITÀ DEGLI STUDI DI PERUGIA

Develop of a plug-in for the Moodle platform, which could facilitate and automate the administration and correction of multiple-choice questionnaires in order to test the knowledge of a large group of university students efficiently.

# EDUCATION AND TRAINING

30/09/2019 - 21/07/2023

MASTER'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE - CURRICULUM ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE Università di Pisa

Final grade 110/110 con Lode

Thesis Leveraging Physical Cues for Learned Representations in Visual Question Answering

19/09/2016 - 19/09/2019

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE Università degli Studi di Perugia

Final grade 110/100 con Lode | Thesis Multidimensional Link Prediction

09/09/2011 - 09/06/2016

ADMINISTRATION, FINANCE AND MARKETING DIPLOMA Istituto R. Bonghi, Assisi

Final grade 98/100

### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **ITALIAN** 

#### Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C1	C1	C1	C1	C1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

# DIGITAL SKILLS

# **Programming Languages**

Python | Latex | C, C++ | Java | HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, AngularJS, PHP | SQL | Solidity

# **Development Tools**

Github, git | Visula Studio Code | Python Anaconda Environmnet | Remix IDE | Eclipse IDE | Piattaforma Remix - Ethereum | Android Studio (sviluppo mobile Android) | Overleaf

# **Programming Skills**

Machine learning | Blockchain e Smart Contract | Big Data Analysis | sviluppo sistema IoT

#### Certificates

Expert.ai ROOKIE certification | Expert.ai PRO certification

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

# **NETWORKS AND MEMBERSHIPS**

28/04/2022 - CURRENT

**Mensa Italia** Mensa is an international no-profit organization open to people who score at the 98th percentile or higher on a standardised, supervised IQ test.

The association has 3 goals:

- 1. Discover and encourage human intelligence for the benefit of human beings.
- 2. Encourage research into the nature, characteristics and uses of intelligence
- 3. Encourage social contacts among Members by means of conferences, discussions, publications, study groups, conventions or other means useful for these purposes